{
    "subject": "resource/Austrian_People's_Party",
    "predicate": "ontology/europeanParliamentGroup",
    "object": "resource/European_People's_Party_Group",
    "human_readable": "The Austrian People's Party is part of the European People's Party Group.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9750800728797913,
            "question": "To which group does the Austrian People's Party belong at the European level?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9692358374595642,
            "question": "What is the name of the European political group that includes the Austrian People's Party?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9331342577934265,
            "question": "Does the Austrian People's Party collaborate with other parties within Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9182396531105042,
            "question": "How is the Austrian People's Party represented in the European Parliament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8968685269355774,
            "question": "How does the Austrian People's Party's membership in the European People's Party Group influence its policies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8553613424301147,
            "question": "What political party is the Austrian People's Party affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8430027365684509,
            "question": "Is the Austrian People's Party part of a larger political alliance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7629628777503967,
            "question": "Can you name some other parties that are part of the European People's Party Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5801313519477844,
            "question": "What kind of political ideology does the European People's Party Group typically represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20881018042564392,
            "question": "What is the significance of belonging to a political group at the European level?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Austrian People's Party is part of the European People's Party Group.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6622_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of political ideology does the European People's Party Group typically represent?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6622_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some other parties that are part of the European People's Party Group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6622_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the Austrian People's Party part of a larger political alliance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6622_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_133.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6622_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to document `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6622/re-ranker-msmarco/74.txt`, it is stated that:\n\n\"On the European stage, the \u00d6VP does not always follow the positions of its European family, the EPP...\"\n\nHowever, later in the same document, it is mentioned that \"The conservative Austrian People\u2019s Party (\u00d6VP/EPP) and The Greens (Die Gr\u00fcnen/EFA) have formed a coalition government since January 1st, 2020.\"\n\nThis implies that \u00d6VP is indeed part of the European People's Party Group (EPP)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that \"The Austrian People's Party (\u00d6VP), a member of the European People\u2019s Party (EPP)\", which supports the statement that \"The Austrian People's Party is part of the European People's Party Group.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}